Best documentary in 2021 Montréal International
First Peoples’ Festival (Présence Autochtone)
Documentary in Construction Prize
of the Ministry of Culture of Peru
CUSCO, PERU
He put me in the center of his words
so to enchant me, right?
The legendary, and ultimately forgotten
Art of Hunting
originally was an exclusively
male privilege and duty.
The "bricheros" aspire to seduce
Western tourists,
to obtain an economic,
material or symbolic benefit.
This Art requires patience above all.
In addition to this quality
it requires fundamental observation.
This is mainly to get into
the head of the prey,
feeling her flesh,
feeling her heartbeat,
to anticipate her moves,
to know where she comes from
and where she goes.
It is dangerous what he is thinking,
what he is teaching.
And in this way,
prepare the ritual,
which from the beginning of time
has always been the same
to get to nail the final bite
in the very center of her heart.
DAMNED WOMANIZER
A documentary by Roberto de la Puente